zamroo.com 2019-10-31

# Zamroo - Free Classifieds | Free Classified Ads | Online Buy & Sell for Free

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Zamroo. (hereafter “Zamroo”, “our,” “we,” or “us”). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our website, mobile applications and other online services (collectively, the “Zamroo Service”) or when you otherwise interact with us.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases; we may provide you with more prominent notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Zamroo Service to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

Acceptance of Terms

Please read this privacy policy carefully since by visiting the Zamroo.com website and/or sharing information with us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time by us with or without notice.

Summary

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our website. In general Zamroo (“Site” or “we”, or “us”) does not collect, use or disclose any data collected with an intention to personally identify and/or contact a person such as: name, address, etc (personally identifying information, hereinafter “Personal Information”) except in specific instances, for example, when you provide Personal Information through registering on the Site or as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Log Files

Like many other online marketplace, we also make use of log files. We automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, mobile number, mobile make and model, including your IP address, when you visit our site, application or service. Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the pages you view. It also contains the additional information like type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, track user’s movement around the site, and gather required demographic information. 

Cookies

To improve the responsiveness of our Website and Mobile Application, we may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the identified computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via website, Application or Service though your computer/laptop or mobile/tablet or any other handheld device etc. 

Opting out

If a user opts out using the Ads Settings, the unique DoubleClick cookie ID on the user's browser is overwritten with the phrase "OPT_OUT". Because there is no longer a unique cookie ID, the opt-out cookie can't be associated with a particular browser.

Web Beacons 

We may use "clear GIFs" (Web Beacons) to track the online usage patterns of our users in an anonymous manner, without personally identifying the user. We may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. We use this information to inter-alia deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our Site, Application or Service to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our Application to improve the Application quality, functionality and interactivity and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come. 

Links to Third Party Sites / Ad Servers

The Website or application may include links to other websites or applications. Such websites or applications are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the application, you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the application's homepage, you should contact the application owners directly for more information.

When we present information to our advertisers, to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our websites or Applications, it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages and content within our websites or Applications. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites or Applications. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number or other personally identifiable information) about your visits to this and other websites or application, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

We do not provide any personally identifiable information to third party websites / advertisers / ad-servers without your consent.

Use of Information

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our website or mobile application. You also authorize Zamroo.com to call or SMS or WhatsApp you in connection with product/service advertised on the platform and you also authorise Zamroo to share your number with other party (buyer/seller) for seamless transaction.

To Target Content and Advertising

To develop and provide you the relevant content and advertising based on your interests, we use the various analytics tools to determine which areas of our website you prefer based upon the frequency of your visits and engagement within those areas. We may also make reasonable geographic and demographic assumptions based on your browser provided data to target relevant content and advertising to you on our site and elsewhere where we may be acting as a 3rd party. 

DART Cookie 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party Ad servers or Ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Zamroo.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons, etc) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

On the Website, Google, as a third-party vendor, uses Cookies to serve ads. Google’s use of the DoubleClick DART Cookie enables it to serve ads to the Website’s users based on their visit to the Websites and Third-Party Websites. 

For more information on the DART Cookie visit: [ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You may opt out of the use of the DART Cookie by Google by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy at: [ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You may opt out of targeting advertising for all NAI member ad networks by visiting: [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

By publishing an ad on this Website, you acknowledge and agree that the Content is public and accessible by any third party and that they may appear in search engine results (such as MSN, Yahoo, Google, Ask and other search engines) and in the cache of those search engines, in feeds and Third-Party Websites pursuant to cobranding agreements, and that it is the sole responsibility of each of those search engines, Third-Party Websites or RSS web feed resources to update and/or to remove Content from their indexes and their cache. You agree and acknowledge that Zamroo is not liable for the information published in search results or by any Third-Party Website that carries Zamroo Ad Listings.

Zamroo.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of other third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Zamroo’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

Information Use by the Company 

The Information as supplied by the users enables us to improve the Services and provide you the most user-friendly experience. In some cases/provision of certain service(s), we may require your contact address as well. All required information is service dependent and the Company may use the above said user Information to, maintain, protect, and improve the Services (including advertising on the "Application") and for developing new services. We may also use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent [with an option to subscribe / unsubscribe (where feasible)]. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major changes, for customer service purposes, new features, new categories, etc).

Any personally identifiable information provided by you will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and / or accessible in the public domain like any comments, messages, blogs, scribbles available on social platforms like facebook, twitter etc.

Any posted/uploaded/conveyed/communicated by users on the public sections of the "Application" becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

In case you choose to decline to submit personally identifiable information on the Application, we may not be able to provide certain services on the Application to you. We will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the same at the time of registering your account. In any case, we will not be liable and or responsible for the denial of certain services to you for lack of you providing the necessary personal information.

When you register with the Application or Services, we contact you from time to time about updation of your personal information to provide the users such features that we believe may benefit / interest you. 

Access, Modification, and Deletion

Once you are registered user, you can see, modify or erase your personal information by signing in to your my account section. Contact customer support at privacy@zamroo.com to review any personal information we store that is not available on Zamroo. There may be a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes during the transaction, enforce our policies; and prevent bad guys from coming back.

Aggregate, Anonymous Information with Advertisers

Zamroo derives revenue from advertising and sharing information is essential to keeping our services Free to users. In order to attract and retain advertisers we use the aggregated, anonymous information that we gather (as well as information from third-party market researchers) to describe our services to partners and to assist our advertisers and sponsors to better understand our user base. We do not disclose personally identifying information about our users to these parties.

Privacy of Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

Links To Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

Information Sharing 

**The Company shares your information with any third party without obtaining the prior consent of the User in the following limited circumstances:**

  1. When it is requested or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms or for complying with the applicable laws and regulations.
  2. The Company may present limited information to our advertisers - to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our websites or Applications – however it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site.
  3. The Company may share your information regarding your activities on websites or Applications with third party social websites to populate your social wall that is visible to other people however you will have an option to set your privacy settings, where you can decide what you would like to share or not to share with others.
  4. **Social Sharing Features.** The Zamroo Service offers social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook, Google+, Twitter sharing button), which let you share actions you take on the Zamroo with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide those features.

As Required By Law

On rare occasions, we may be required to disclose your personal information due to legal or regulatory requirements. In such instances, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required in order to comply with our legal obligations, including but not limited to complying with court orders, warrants, service of process requirements, or discovery requests. We may also disclose information about our users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce these Terms and/or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Zamroo, our users or the general public. You agree and acknowledge that we may not inform you prior to or after disclosures made according to this section. By any chance, if we sell whole or part of our business, the acquiring entity shall have access to your personal information without your consent and we may send you a notice regarding this sale.

Changes To This Privacy Policy

As we continue to expand the Services and to improve the user experience;, this policy may change, so please refer back to this privacy policy periodically. By accessing the website or the mobile application or otherwise using the Services, you consent to collection, storage, and use of the personal information you provide (including any changes thereto as provided by you) for any of the services that we offer.

Complaints

Any complaints, abuse or concerns with regards to the processing of information provided by you or breach of these terms shall be immediately informed to the Grievance Officer as mentioned below via email signed with the electronic signature to [complaints@zamroo.com](mailto:complaints@zamroo.com)

**We request you to please provide the following information in your complaint:**

  1. Identification of the information provided by you;
  2. Clear statement as to whether the information is personal information or any business information;
  3. Your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address;
  4. A statement that you have a good-faith belief that the information has been processed incorrectly or disclosed without authorization, as the case may be;
  5. A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notice is accurate, and that the information being complained about belongs to you;
  6. If it is related to any particular listing, than mention the Ad ID and other details you may have.
  7. You may also contact us in case you have any questions / suggestions about the Privacy Policy using the contact information mentioned above.

**The company shall not be responsible for any communication, if addressed, to any non-designated person in this regard.**

How to Contact Us

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [privacy@zamroo.com](mailto:privacy@zamroo.com). We do read every message submitted to us and we always try to reply promptly to everyone ASAP.

Zamroo reserves the right to withdraw and/or alter any or all of the Privacy Policy of the plan at any time without prior notice.
